He said that in the stock market, on December 14, the shopkeeper's
Sun Sex Bazaar News of two thousand rupees, all the Bank confirmed
midcaps are
in the red,
Lalmani is red
and absolutely grade
Sensex-Nifty Nifty Bank Nifty
Midcap Fund, a lot of them are in the red,
so let me tell you
that the stocks that are watched, out of the
17100 numbers,
are in the 293 rate,
sorry, 940 is in the rate, I am talking about the number around eighteen hundred,
and 893, that is, nine hundred, is in the green,
again I will repeat that thing that I keep on saying this
continuously and keep on saying
and will keep on saying that until you
say it openly, now we will also keep
investing in the stock market with the idea
that the work of the market is to go up and
down, it is the rule of the market to go up and down, it is the nature of the
market to go up and
down, hence it does not make any difference to us either,
as Chaap Bhai keeps on repeating this thing,
I will definitely say that
I do not have much effect on the up or down of the trend.  I do
n't have to give it, it does
n't matter much to me, I just consider it an
indication that there may have been a softening in one stock
and the market may have fallen or there may have been
some reduction in the suggestion. If you tell me,
even after these four lifelines being in the red zone, the Nifty
Sensex rates, which I had said very
strongly yesterday and I repeated it many times.
And after all, you will also see the last video.
I said, where did I say
that Nestle should be in your prime back, that's why
I bought
Nestle Labs, that's why I bought it.
Today's low price is 287
rupees, the high is
19270 rupees. So,
yesterday I had said very strongly for Power Grid, with the rupee being on the
outside at 45 rupees. I had
said very strongly for Divi's Labs, it is on the outside. Even after this red low is
not there, now you tell me what does the
market fall and the market crash and all these
things have to do with it. The video that is
uploaded on YouTube is absolutely
on record. You should watch yesterday's video. That's
why I said it was said, I had
not told you that it had happened.  Where did I buy the tablet,
so love David, I said or not,
network, I said with five to ten repetitions
that Nestle should be your best buy in English
and that's why I bought it and
write down a lot further, I bought it for a lot of strength,
I bought it for a lot of profit
and I repeated this many times
that my three geniuses, I have this less, page
26, it has reached 40,000, oh the
boss of 11000 has reached around 16 thousand, less they have
also reached our students, it is definitely
moving at a snail's pace but I can tell you that
it will
complete its journey and it will
definitely reach my target, I asked for Ice Ice
Lamba, told you for the next flight,
yesterday JK Cement is
on continuous recommendation, you should look at MCX,
where did it go, you have to understand this thing, today there is no
price in Arvindo Pharma,
sir, there is no
price in my company, if
you buy then look at the sale, then
Kaushani has come down to the price of 114, again my list is
mine, I am giving this word  This is going to be
ten times more than the
city price in 10 years, I will do a
complete video for that
as I did for the first time
for ITC, is this my complete single video on any company
but I am in the second year and
third year, I want to do it on shares and Coal India,
when such facility is there or I get an
opportunity, I will definitely do it,
see the rise in Infosys today, friend, see,
Astro is a very good and lively
share, when you buy in all these things,
you keep buying, what is the problem in it,
see the rise today, 225 is above that,
but the system was 3938, at that time people were scared,
when will you come to 4440 today, that is my continuous
recommendation of President System and in
future also I am convinced and with this, they have increased their numbers,
these few have crossed 516,
according to Durga Puja, when the market
falls, the market is weak, the prices
come down, today Deepak Laddoo is at such a great price, if
you want to buy Police, buy this fridge, Deepak
Next  Buy Balaji Amines,
all these shares are 2865 Prince, the story of a
person's nature, bought at Gaya Palika,
bought 3G loot even in scarcity,
write it down in this price, so you have to see how
wisely you buy in the stock market, with what courage
and at what opportunity you buy all the things,
Addiction Technology, today
which I call a loser, Wheeler, today
is an opportunity for you, there is 157 shares in Piramal Enterprises,
today is an opportunity for you, there is more shares
in Shriram Transport, today is an opportunity for
you, there is 166 shares in Digital Technology,
you can buy 150 shares in Infosys
through purchase, the prices of all these shares are
much higher from here and
you will get very good targets from them, Kotak Mahindra
Bank, in the end, that recommendation is my
strong claim, strong buy, Kotak
Mahindra Bank, Mahindra Mahindra Finance,
both will give you good profits on this and
buy Bajaj Finance with a bag full and the
long one which came back by one and a half inch from here, the
day it broke the limit of 8000,
then you will not come below that and 7008
market  There is a gap of ₹100 between 16000 and 16000.
Reliance Bajaj Finance and Bajaj
Finserv are on my list of good buys. Please
note that if it works for you, then
definitely buy it. That's all
for today and we will talk again after today's market.
One more last thing I want to know is how I can go about
sharing my opinion. Buy Torch on
Titan because there will be a
lot in Reliance and it has a very long
target. I will not do Star's Disc,
but Reliance and Titan are my
first shares. Today, according to the price, I am
also adding Britannia and Report to the pan-city market.
About India, a
person has also bought from Nestle in 18164. You
must buy Report India and
keep Nestle in the buy list because Nestle is currently
preparing to take off from its place. And
finally, I would say that HDFC HUL, which is
my pair of two swans, definitely
keep some purchases in it.
If you can, then the boss
is very pending for the target. I can tell you about it
and in the coming time, all these
stocks are very wonderful, vibrant and strong markets.
Instead of up or down, it does not matter to them
or the companies that are going ahead, the
companies that are going to grow and the
stock market of this India is full of
companies that are going to do well, they will remain strong
and will keep increasing your money as well,
so you should invest in such scripts in
which the risk is very low and the risk
zone-2 should also run so that
you get many times less money in it,
if it ever comes then I will
tell you, by the way, from obscene India,
if I say Refer India and
Nazara Technology, I like them very much,
you can buy them, Tata Chemicals
and Tata Elxsi, L&T Infotech and Related
Technology, all these are players of danger,
but these Ishare shares are a little high in their price,
but in real India, in All India
Winter, you
can take it as a relationship and for continuous earning,
my second son is like a son, which I have
noted in my diary, the second share is
IDF Bank and
Seconds, add in it that Jubilant Food, that's all
for today, Sadhu stock market people said
that the shop in the stock market will open today, 4th
December, 2000, see you again.
After the market, there will be a discussion on the market, there will be a discussion on the new city and the new
market, there will be a
discussion, we will meet again, it is
open, I missed it.